[HUMMING, BUZZING]
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
SUBTITLES BY EXPLOSIVESKULL
[WIND HOWLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAN RAPPING INDISTINCTLY]
♪ WHERE ALL THE FUCKING
WHITE HATS HANG OUT ♪
♪ COME DOWN TO WESTERN PLAZA ♪
♪ WHERE KING'S ♪
♪ 'BOUT TO FUCK SHIT UP! ♪
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[CROWD CLAMORING]
[LAUGHTER, CLAMORING CONTINUES]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
IT'S NOW OR NEVER,
MOTHERFUCKERS!
WE END THIS SHIT TONIGHT.
[CAMERON]
"DESTROY EVERYTHING."
IS THIS THE MESSAGE WE WANT
TO SEND OUR CHILDREN
FOR GENERATIONS TO COME?
"DESTROY... EVERYTHING."
THIS, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
IS WHAT THAT
WEAPON-WIELDING GOON WORE
THE NIGHT OF THE ALTERCATION.
LOOKS TO ME LIKE
HE WAS ON
A MISSION TO KILL.
COMBAT BOOTS,
WAR CHAINS...
AND THIS.
"DESTROY EVERYTHING."
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING ON TV]
[MARILYN MANSON ON TV]
HOW'S IT GOING, NEW YORK?
I CHOSE TO SPEAK TO YOU
IN A SQUARE
BECAUSE I THINK WE'RE KIND OF
CONDITIONED TO LISTEN TO PEOPLE,
WHEN THEY'RE IN
THE SHAPE OF A SQUARE.
AND ALSO, HERE IN HOLLYWOOD,
THIS IS WHERE WE GIVE PEOPLE
WHAT THEY WANT.
VIOLENCE, I GUESS THAT'S WHAT
IT SEEMS TO COME DOWN TO.
WHAT I WANTED TO TALK TO
EVERYONE TODAY ABOUT,
UH... I DON'T REALLY
WANT TO PREACH,
I JUST WANT TO, MORE,
BRING UP SOME QUESTIONS.
AND SINCE I ALWAYS
TEND TO BE
A SCAPEGOAT, I THOUGHT
WE'D TALK ABOUT BLAME.
RIGHT NOW,
EVERYBODY WANTS TO BLAME MUSIC,
THEY WANT TO
BLAME MOVIES,
BUT, UH... YOU KNOW,
WE'VE FORGOTTEN
THAT WE HAVE A DEAD GUY
HANGING FROM A TREE
IN OUR LIVING ROOMS.
UH... UH...
AND THAT'S SOMETHING THAT WE'VE
WORSHIPPED ALL OUR LIVES.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT
THE CRUCIFIX AS THE...
THE GREATEST MASS-MARKET
PIECE OF MERCHANDISE
IN THE HISTORY OF THE WORLD.
I'VE ALWAYS FOUND IT
TO BE KIND OF INTERESTING.
WE HAVEN'T REALLY SAT DOWN AND
TALKED ABOUT THAT ON THE NEWS.
UM... ALSO, WONDERED
WHY NOBODY CARES WHEN
AN ADULT COMMITS SOME
SENSELESS ACT OF VIOLENCE
THEY WANT TO HAVE
A REASON WHY.
THAT'S ONLY WHEN
A KID DOES IT.
BUT I THINK WHAT'S REALLY...
BEGUN TO CONFUSE PEOPLE NOW
AND WHY WE'RE IN THIS STATE
OF... UH, CHAOS
AND, UH, PC, NONSENSICAL,
UPTIGHTNESS.
IT'S WHITE TEENAGERS.
THAT'S THE REAL ENIGMA.
WHY ARE THEY MAD?
THEY'RE MIDDLE CLASS,
THEY'RE WHITE,
THEY'RE SPOILED.
IS IT BECAUSE THEY KNOW
AMERICA'S A LIE?
IS IT BECAUSE
WE MAKE THEM FEEL
LIKE THEY'RE NEVER
GOOD ENOUGH, YOU KNOW?
"YOU'RE NEVER GOOD ENOUGH
FOR THE SCHOLARSHIP,
FOR THE CAR, FOR THE GIRL.
NEVER GOOD ENOUGH TO BE
FAMOUS FOR 15 MINUTES."
AND THEN, ARE WE SURPRISED
WHY THEY'RE MAD
OR WHY THEY END UP DEAD,
YOU KNOW?
WHY THE VIOLENCE?
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW...
YOU MADE THEM, AMERICA.
YOU KNOW,
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
[CROWD CHANTING IN DISTANCE]
[MARCHING BAND PLAYING,
CHANTING]
COME ON, GET YOUR GAME DAY
SPORTS STUFF.
SHIT, YEAH.
HEY, QUIT MESSING AROUND, MAN.
WHY? I DON'T EVEN SEE WHY YOUR
BITCH-ASS NEEDS A HELMET ANYWAY.
JV HAS NO BUSINESS
SUITING UP.
[MCCORMICK]
COME ON NOW, RICKY.
HE MIGHT SEE THE FIELD.
WE'LL HAVE THEIR ASS BEAT
BY HALFTIME, YOU KNOW THAT.
MCCORMICK, YOU ACT LIKE IT'S
HARD TO BE A LINEMAN, MAN.
ALL YOU DO IS SIT ON
YOUR FAT ASS AND EAT.
BUDDY, ONLY THING I'M EATING
IS YOUR MOM'S PUSSY.
- [SPITS]
- [GIGGLES]
WHAT... GET...
GET THE FUCK OFF ME!
QUIT FREAKIN' PLAYING
GRAB-ASS, MAN!
IT'S A PLAYOFF GAME!
ACT LIKE IT!
LET IT GO, CODY.
COME ON,
LET'S BRING IT IN, MEN.
[ALL]
OUR FATHER, WHO ART IN HEAVEN,
HALLOWED BY THY NAME.
THY KINGDOM COME,
THY WILL BE DONE,
ON EARTH AS IT IS
IN HEAVEN.
GIVE US THIS DAY
OUR DAILY BREAD.
AND FORGIVE US
OUR TRESPASSES,
AS WE FORGIVE THOSE
WHO TRESPASS AGAINST US.
AND LEAD US NOT
INTO TEMPTATION,
BUT DELIVER US FROM EVIL.
FOR THINE IS THE KINGDOM,
THE POWER,
THE GLORY FOREVER
- AND EVER.
- HEY, WHAT'S UP, BRI?
GOOD TO SEE YOU, MAN.
- WHERE YOU BEEN?
- NEW YORK.
GOOD, YEAH.
THE SHOW'S ALREADY GOING ON.
[BRIAN]
THE SHOW MUST GO ON!
HEY, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
- MY BROTHER INSIDE?
- YEAH, HE'S IN THERE SOMEWHERE.
[PUNK ROCK BAND PLAYING]
HOW WE LOOKING?
UH, GOOD...
WHAT'S UP, DAWG?
[GROANS]
YEAH!
WHAT THE FUCK!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- DUDE!
- OH!
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
BRIAN?
BRIAN! DUDE!
[CHUCKLES]
NO, NO, NO, I AIN'T
LETTING YOU OFF THAT EASY.
GET YOUR ASS UP HERE
AND DO THE SONG LIST.
[LAUGHS]
GET UP HERE.
[OVER P.A.] LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS DUDE RIGHT HERE...
[CYMBALS CRASHING LIGHTLY]
WE WOULDN'T BE HERE
IF IT WASN'T FOR
THIS KID RIGHT HERE!
[CHEERING]
[MAN IN CROWD WHISTLES]
CHEERS, BRO.
[BAND TUNING UP]
[SPITS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ THE LIST ♪
♪ IS THOUSANDS LONG ♪
♪ PEOPLE WHO DECIDED ♪
♪ IT WASN'T FOR THEM ♪
♪ DID THEY REALLY ♪
♪ MAKE THAT DECISION? ♪
♪ CONDITIONING RUNS DEEP ♪
♪ IN THE USA ♪
♪ TEENAGE REBELLION ♪
♪ IS JUST FINE ♪
♪ AS LONG AS ♪
♪ YOU STOP ♪
♪ WHEN YOU TURN 18 ♪
♪ THOUSANDS OF PUNKS TURNED
TO SOCIETY'S TOOLS ♪
♪ THERE'S SOMETHING
IN THEIR EYES ♪
♪ YOU CAN TELL THEY SOLD OUT ♪
♪ REMEMBER PUNK IS MORE THAN ♪
♪ TEENAGE REBELLION ♪
♪ SURE, IT STARTS THERE,
BUT WHY DOES IT END? ♪
♪ AND THE LIST ♪
♪ IS THOUSANDS LONG. ♪
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
[MARCHING BAND PLAYING]
[BAND CONTINUES PLAYING INSIDE]
HEY, YOU GOT A LIGHT?
YOU KNOW THOSE THINGS TAKE
14 MINUTES OFF YOUR LIFE
EVERY TIME YOU SMOKE
ONE OF THEM?
WHAT ARE YOU, A PSYCHIC?
I ONLY SMOKE WHEN I DRINK.
YEAH, HOW MUCH HAVE YOU
HAD TO DRINK TONIGHT?
WELL, I'M SORRY, THE GUY
WHO CAN DOWN A 40 OUNCE BEER
IN LIKE FIVE SECONDS
IS QUESTIONING ME
ABOUT DRINKING?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
A BOTTLE OF MALT LIQUOR A DAY
KEEPS THE DOCTOR AWAY.
REALLY?
AND HOW MANY BOTTLES
HAVE YOU HAD TONIGHT?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
[BOTTLE BREAKS]
AAH!
LOOK AT THIS FUCKER.
WHAT'S HAPPENING, MAN?
OOH!
[CHUCKLES]
SHIT, I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D MAKE IT BACK IN TIME.
I'M NOT GONNA
MISS THE SHOW.
THOUGHT WE LOST YOU
TO THE ROAD.
PSH. SHOULD'VE KNOWN THIS BLACK
HOLE WOULD SUCK YOU BACK IN.
- NEVER FAILS.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
KILLER SHOW.
GLAD TO HAVE YOU BACK.
[OLES]
FUCK YEAH, DAWG.
[CHUCKLES]
FUCK.
FUCKED MY ANKLE UP
IN THERE.
SHUT THE FUCK UP, KING,
ALL RIGHT?
DUDE.
ALL RIGHT, SUNSHINE,
TELL THIS ASSHOLE
THAT SKINHEADS ARE RACIST.
FIRST OF ALL,
STOP CALLING ME "SUNSHINE."
READ A FUCKING BOOK.
THIS SHIT WAS STARTED
WAY BEFORE
ANY OF THAT RACIST SHIT
CAME AROUND.
- HE'S RIGHT, IT GOES WAY BACK.
- STRAIGHT UP, THOUGH.
STRAIGHT-LACED BITCH.
OKAY, FUCK Y'ALL.
CRASS, LET'S ROLL, COME ON.
CATCH UP WITH Y'ALL
IN A BIT.
YO, HELP ME CLEAN
SOME SHIT UP.
[WOMAN]
HEY! THERE HE IS!
[GROUP CLAMORING]
[BRIAN]
TINY HUMAN.
WHAT'S UP, DUDE?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
WHAT'S UP?
JAKE.
[BRIAN GRUNTS]
- DIGGING THAT HAT.
- OH, THIS?
- YEAH, IT'S PRETTY SWEET.
- [LAUGHS]
YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME
AT THE SHOW?
IT WAS A DAMN GOOD SHOW.
[LAUGHS]
ACTUALLY,
IT'S MY FIRST SHOW.
- NO FUCKING WAY.
- YEAH.
I GOT AN IDEA.
COME WITH ME.
COME ON.
HEY, YO!
- YO.
- YO, I WANT TO INTRODUCE YOU TO MY LITTLE BUDDY, JAKE.
HE JUST GOT HIS CONCERT CHERRY
POPPED TONIGHT.
HELL YEAH, LITTLE DUDE.
YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME?
YEAH, FOR SURE.
STARTING THEM YOUNG,
LOVE IT. [LAUGHS]
- THAT'S HOW WE DO IT.
- YEAH.
HEY, WOULD YOU SIGN MY HAT?
OF COURSE.
[BRIAN LAUGHS]
HERE YOU ARE.
- YO, THANKS.
- YOU GOT IT, BRO.
THAT'S WHAT'S UP.
- SEE YOU LATER.
- ALL RIGHT. YO...
IT'S NOT MUCH...
- AH.
- ...BUT HERE'S YOUR CUT.
HELL YEAH.
THANKS, MAN.
- LONG AS WE MAKE IT TO THE 505, IT'S ALL GOOD.
- THAT SHOULD DO THE TRICK.
DUDE...
THANK YOU.
YOU GOT IT.
KILLER SHOW.
[DJ OVER RADIO] WELL, UNLESS
YOU'VE BEEN LIVING UNDER A ROCK,
I'M SURE YOU HEARD THE OUTCOME
OF TONIGHT'S 5-8
DIVISION I QUARTERFINAL
PLAYOFF GAME
BETWEEN THE REBELS
AND THE RABBITS,
AND BOY WAS IT UGLY.
THAT IS, IF YOU WERE
ROOTING FOR THE REBELS.
46 TO 3,
YOU HEARD THAT RIGHT, FOLKS.
BETTER LUCK
NEXT SEASON, REBELS.
[SIGHS]
WHAT DO Y'ALL
WANT TO DO NOW?
I GUESS GET WASTED. I MEAN,
WHAT'S BETTER TO DO IN THIS TOWN?
YEAH, IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE HAD A BEER.
YEAH, WELL,
IT'S NOW OR NEVER.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
FUCK.
IT'S 12:15.
SON OF A BITCH.
[DAVIS]
DUMBASS LAWS, MAN.
[COUNTRY MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[PUNK ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING FROM CAR STEREO]
♪ WE WISH THAT WE COULD
FUCK SHIT UP! ♪
[MUSIC, ENGINE STOPS]
[PUNKS LAUGHING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
FROSTY!
- WHAT'S UP, BOSS?
- WHAT UP, WHAT UP?
HEY, YOU GOT TO COME
TO OUR NEXT SHOW, BRO.
I'M TELLING YOU,
YOU'LL LOVE IT.
THANKS, BOSS.
- FUCK YEAH.
- [CODY] IT'S GONNA TAKE A LOT OF PRAYING
- TO FIX THAT FREAK SHOW.
- [MCCORMICK] FUCKING PUSSIES.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[COUNTRY MUSIC CONTINUES
OVER SPEAKERS]
FOR YOU, PRINCESS.
FOR YOU.
ME FIRST.
MY LOVE.
AW, HOW SWEET.
BRO-BRO.
- SO... [CHUCKLES]
- MM-HMM.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THAT
WE SHOULD GIVE IT A TRY,
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
ME AND YOU TOGETHER...
♪ FOREVER. ♪
[CLICKS TONGUE]
UM...
YEAH. MAYBE.
- YEAH! SHE SAID "YES"!
- [CHUCKLES]
- WHAT'S UP, FAGGOT?
- FUCK AROUND AND FIND OUT.
[CODY]
YOU'RE A FUCKING FREAK, MAN.
[MCCORMICK]
FUCKING PUSSY.
- FUCKING TWEAKER REEKS.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
[OLES] THAT BITCH-ASS MOTHERFUCKER'S
ABOUT TO GET FUCKING BOXED, DAWG.
- [KING] WHICH ONE?
- [OLES] THAT FUCKING BITCH-ASS RIGHT THERE
WITH THE FUCKING TIE.
THOSE FUCKING LOSERS, MAN.
THINK THEY MIGHT
LIKE YOU, CODY.
- FUCK YOU, MCCORMICK.
- [LAUGHS]
[KING]
YOU GOT MY NIGHTSTICK, BRO?
[OLES]
YEAH.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES]
- AW, YOU PIECE OF SHIT.
- [LAUGHS]
WHAT, BITCH?
FUCK YOU.
OH, YEAH?
WHAT'S UP, WHAT'S UP?
WHAT, BITCH?
- DUDE, CHILL THE FUCK OUT, DAWG.
- WHAT, BITCH?
- DO SOMETHING.
- LET'S GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
- DO SOMETHING, BRUH.
- FUCK YOU TOO, BITCH.
- WHOA, "BITCH"?
I'M TRYING TO MAINTAIN
THE PEACE, DAWG.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO FUCK WITH ME, FOOL.
IF IT'S ON,
IT'S FUCKING ON.
SUCK MY DICK,
YOU FUCKING FREAK SHOW.
- "FREAK SHOW"?
- I'LL SHOW YOU FREAK SHOW
WHEN I BASH
YOUR DOME IN, BRUH. HUH?
I'M GONNA BASH
YOUR FUCKING DOME IN, DAWG!
FROSTY:
HEY, HEY, HEY!
HEY, GOD DAMN IT.
HEY, HEY,
TAKE IT OUTSIDE!
- [CLAMORING]
- LET'S GO, OUTSIDE!
I'M CALLING
THE DAMN COPS. OUTSIDE!
- OUTSIDE!
- HEY, HEY!
[ALL CLAMORING]
- HEY, WHAT NOW, BITCH?
- I'M GONNA FUCK YOU UP.
WHERE YOU GOING, DAWG?
WHERE YOU GOING, MAN?
YO, YOU'RE LUCKY YOUR FAGGOT FUCKING
FRIENDS ARE HERE TO SAVE YOU.
OH, THEY GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS, MAN.
THIS GOT EVERYTHING TO DO
WITH YOU, ME,
THAT PUSSY-ASS
LOOK ON YOUR FACE
AND MY FUCKING FRIEND
HERE, MAN!
- OH, YOU LIKE THAT?
- [CODY] FUCK YOU,
YOU FUCKING PIECE OF SHIT.
THAT'S RIGHT, BITCH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
ROLL THE FUCK OUT.
ROLL THE FUCK OUT, BRUH.
- THE FUCK YOU GOING, BRUH?
- YO!
[KING]
HA-HA!
[OLES] FUCK YEAH,
THAT'S RIGHT, BITCH!
[KING]
HEY, HE'S COMING BACK,
HE'S COMING BACK,
HE'S COMING BACK.
GET THE FUCK
OUT OF HERE.
[CHUCKLES]
[ENGINE RUNNING]
[LAUGHTER, CHEERING]
[CAMERON]
PLEASE TELL THE COURT
HOW YOU WOULD
DESCRIBE YOURSELF,
YOUR LIFESTYLE.
I DON'T KNOW.
PUNK?
"PUNK"?
FUNNY YOU WOULD SAY THAT.
BECAUSE WEBSTER'S DICTIONARY...
GIVES US
THE FOLLOWING DEFINITION
OF THIS TERM
YOU SO ELOQUENTLY USE
TO DESCRIBE YOURSELF: PUNK.
"A WORTHLESS PERSON;
AN OFTEN AGGRESSIVE
OR VIOLENT YOUNG MAN,
USUALLY A PETTY HOODLUM
OR GANGSTER;
A SOCIOPATH."
IT'S NOT ABOUT
A DEFINITION.
I WOULDN'T EXPECT
SOMEONE LIKE YOU...
TO UNDERSTAND THAT.
OH, WELL, THEN
PLEASE HELP ME.
HELP THE JURY UNDERSTAND
HOW WEARING CHAINS
AND MILITARY CLOTHING
IS JUST PART
OF THE STYLE,
AND NOT WEAPONS
AT THE READY.
IT'S A STATEMENT.
OH, YOU ARE CORRECT,
IT MOST CERTAINLY IS
A STATEMENT.
BUT IT IS NOT A STATEMENT
OF FASHION,
IT'S A STATEMENT OF
MALICIOUS INTENT.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[TRAIN HORN SOUNDING
IN THE DISTANCE]
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
[OLES GROANS]
MY HEAD'S POUNDING.
IT'S NOT YOUR HEAD, MAN,
THERE'S SOMEONE AT THE DOOR.
HERSCHEL,
WHAT'S HAPPENING, MAN?
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
RENT WAS DUE LAST WEEK.
AH, I KNOW, I DO.
I GOT A LITTLE BEHIND.
HERE'S THIS.
IT'S SHORT.
I KNOW.
BUT JUST GIVE US
A LITTLE BIT MORE TIME,
AND I PROMISE
I'LL GET YOU THE REST.
I LIKE YOU ALL
AND WHAT YOU'RE DOING AND ALL,
BUT I NEED THE MONEY.
I CAN'T HAVE Y'ALL
SQUATTING IN HERE.
I'M ALREADY GIVING YOU
A BREAK ON PRICE, MAN.
I KNOW.
AND WE APPRECIATE IT.
[SIGHS]
I'M JUST... I'M TRYING.
YOU KNOW, IT'S...
DUDE, YOU KNOW
I'M GOOD FOR IT.
THESE SHOWS, THEY'RE STARTING
TO GO REALLY WELL.
I JUST NEED LIKE A WEEK
AND I'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
ALL RIGHT, BUT THAT'S IT.
ALL RIGHT?
I'M SERIOUS THIS TIME.
I HONESTLY CAN'T WAIT
ANY LONGER, ALL RIGHT?
ONE WEEK OR I GOT TO
LOCK IT UP, MAN.
OKAY. AND, HERSCHEL,
THANK YOU.
I PROMISE,
YOU WON'T REGRET THIS.
- ALL RIGHT.
- I PROMISE.
THANK YOU.
ONE WEEK!
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN,
THEN CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MIKE]
YOU KNOW, IT'S GONNA BE HARD
FOR YOU TO GET A JOB
LOOKING LIKE A WILD INDIAN.
[BRIAN] DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, OLD
MAN, I GOT A FEW THINGS LINED UP.
OH, I'M NOT WORRIED,
THAT'S YOUR MOTHER'S JOB.
I GUESS A HELMET'S OUT
OF THE QUESTION, TOO.
I'M NOT TRYING
TO LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT.
[CHUCKLES]
YOU COULD'VE FOOLED ME.
- [MIKE GRUNTS]
- [REPORTER ON TV] HOW DANGEROUS...
[MIKE LAUGHS MOCKINGLY]
[MAN ON TV] THIS IS THE LAST
OF THE MEGADEATH WEAPONS.
- A HUGE BOMB, NINE MEGATONS.
- [SPATULA CLATTERING]
IT HAS MORE EXPLOSIVE POWER
THAN ALL THE MISSILES FIRED
FROM ONE OF OUR NUCLEAR-ARMED
SUBMARINES TODAY.
AND COULD BE DETONATED
BY A VARIETY OF WAYS:
A SPARK, A LIGHTNING STORM
OR EVEN A HIT
COULD SET IT OFF.
[REPORTER] BUT WE HAVE
DISMANTLED OTHERS LIKE THIS...
WHO WERE YOU TALKING TO
OUT THERE?
RAN INTO AN OLD FRIEND.
- [GASPS]
- TOLD YOU I'D COME.
OH! WHO IS THIS?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I THINK,
I'M GONNA TAKE YOU DOWN
TO TRACY AND SHE'LL GIVE YOU
A GOOD HAIRCUT.
OH!
SOUNDS LIKE
A GOOD IDEA TO ME.
I SAY YOU JUST SHAVE
THE WHOLE THING.
MAKE YOU LOOK
LIKE A REAL MAN.
[BRIAN]
SMELLS GOOD, MA.
- YOU MAKE ENOUGH FOR EVERYBODY?
- BETWEEN YOU AND YOUR BROTHER,
I NEVER KNOW
WHO'S GONNA BE HERE
SO I ALWAYS TRY.
OH, AND YOU CAN TAKE SOME
TO YOUR FRIENDS, TOO.
I'M SURE THEY COULD USE A GOOD
MEAL EVERY ONCE AND A WHILE.
NOT TRYING TO FEED
THE WHOLE NEIGHBORHOOD.
[TV CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY
IN THE BACKGROUND]
WHAT'S COOKING, BETTY?
OH.
[CHUCKLES]
- YUMMY.
- COME ON, MAN.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S STRANGE,
I NEVER HEARD
ANYONE KNOCK.
VERY FUNNY, MR. D.
YOU BOYS CUT IT OUT.
HELP YOURSELF, JOHN.
THANK YOU, BETTY.
HEY, PASS THE EGGS, MAN.
I AIN'T HERE
TO SERVE YOU.
GET UP AND
GET THEM YOURSELF.
YOU LOOKING FOR THIS?
WHAT THE HELL, MOM?
THE NAME OF YOUR BAND IS
"WHITE SLAVE TRADERS"?
WE'RE ALL SLAVES
TO AUTHORITY, MA.
[BIRDS CALLING]
[PUNK MUSIC PLAYING LOUDLY
OVER STEREO]
[JASON] GET YOUR ASS OVER
HERE AND HELP ME REAL QUICK.
[BRIAN] DON'T TELL ME WHAT
TO DO, I'M AN ANARCHIST!
[JASON]
KISS MY ASS.
[BRIAN] I WOULD, BUT I DON'T
WANT MY LIPS TO STINK.
[JASON GRUNTS]
SHIT!
[BRIAN CHUCKLES]
OH, WELL.
WHY DO WE
DO THIS SHIT, MAN?
'CAUSE IT'S FUN!
THIS IS WORK,
NOT FUN.
IT'S BOTH.
PLUS, WE'RE MAKING
A MARK ON THIS TOWN.
THIS TOWN
DON'T GIVE A SHIT.
SHIT, I KNOW, BUT...
THAT "AMARILLIONARE"
GAVE US SOME EXTRA CASH.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
GOT TO LOVE THAT KOOKY BASTARD.
[BRIAN] YEP, HE'S
ALWAYS BEEN GOOD TO US.
YEAH, I COULD DEFINITELY
USE THE CASH.
[CAN OPENS,
TOP RATTLES IN CAN]
[BRIAN LAUGHS]
[JASON]
NO, BUT FOR REAL, THOUGH,
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
MAN, I JUST WANT TO START
BOOKING BIGGER BANDS, YOU KNOW?
I FEEL LIKE THE SCENE'S
- REALLY PICKING UP.
- IT'S ALL POSSIBLE, MAN,
YOU JUST GOT TO
GET THE BANDS
TO MAKE THE STOP.
YOU JUST LET ME WORRY
ABOUT THAT, ALL RIGHT?
HEY, YOU MIND
LOCKING UP?
YEAH, MAN,
WHERE YOU GOING?
- I JUST GOT SOME SHIT TO TAKE CARE OF, NO BIG DEAL.
- NEED A LIFT?
NO, NO, I'M GOOD,
I'LL MEET UP WITH Y'ALL LATER.
ALL RIGHT, MAN.
HEY, I GOT A SURPRISE
FOR Y'ALL TONIGHT, TOO.
I THINK I MIGHT
KNOW WHAT IT IS.
THINK IT'S READY?
I THINK IT'S CLOSE.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[TRAIN HORN SOUNDING]
[TRAIN BELL CLANGING]
[CAR ALARM SOUNDING
IN THE DISTANCE]
[MUSIC PLAYING
FROM CAR STEREO]
- WHOO-HOO!
- [RICKY] WHAT THE FUCK
- IS UP WITH YOUR HAIR?
- GOT OURSELVES A PRETTY ONE, BOYS.
- WHAT ARE YOU, AN EL CHUPACABRA-LOOKING MOTHERFUCKER?
- [BRIAN] WHAT'S UP, DAWG?
- [MCCORMICK] WHAT'S UP, BABY?
- [RICKY] THE FUCK YOU SAY? HUH?
PRETTY-HAIRED
LITTLE PUSSY.
- OH, LOOK AT THIS LITTLE SHIT.
- WHOO-HOO!
I FUCKED A GIRL
IN A PAIR OF JEANS
LIKE THAT.
[RICKY]
SHIT HEAD!
- LET'S GO! LET'S GO, RICKY!
- [GIGGLES]
WHOO-HOO-HOO!
FUCK YOU!
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[MUSIC PLAYING
OVER STEREO]
[ROME GIGGLES]
DAMN!
WATCH THE JACKET.
MY BAD, MY BAD.
- YOU OKAY?
- YEAH.
CHILL OUT,
IT'S ALL GOOD.
DON'T JUST SIT THERE,
GET UP
AND GET THE LADY
ANOTHER BEER.
WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
THIS WHOLE TOWN
IS BUILT TO SUPPORT
THE ONLY NUCLEAR WEAPONS
MANUFACTURING FACILITY
IN THE NATION.
PUT IT TOGETHER, IF YOU WERE
GOING TO ATTACK AMERICA,
WOULDN'T YOU TRY TO TAKE OUT THEIR
MOST VULNERABLE WEAPONS FIRST?
WE GOT
PLUTONIUM WAR HEADS
UNDER OUR FEET
AS WE SPEAK.
THIS PLACE IS JUST
A BIG TARGET, TICKING.
TICKING AWAY.
BOMB FUCKING CITY.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
THANKS.
[MUSIC PLAYING AND INDISTINCT
CONVERSATIONS IN THE BACKGROUND]
THANKS.
DUDE, OF COURSE.
CAN YOU PROMISE ME SOMETHING?
I DON'T LIKE PROMISES.
WHATEVER,
JUST HEAR ME OUT.
SURE, GO AHEAD.
YOU MAY THINK THIS SOUNDS
CHEESY OR WHATEVER...
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
JUST...
PLEASE...
I...
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO LEAVE HERE...
WITHOUT BEING
ARMED SOMEHOW.
WE NEED EQUALIZERS.
AND NOT JUST YOU,
I MEAN, ALL OF US.
SO, WHAT, LIKE KING
AND HIS POLICE BATON?
I THINK I CAN
HANDLE MYSELF.
I KNOW.
BUT...
I DON'T KNOW, LIKE,
DUMB SHIT LIKE THIS,
IT HAPPENS
ALL THE TIME.
I'LL JUST GET, LIKE, A ROCKET
LAUNCHER OR DRIVE A TANK,
THEN NO ONE WILL
MESS WITH ME THEN.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
HOW ABOUT
A BAZOOKA, THEN?
SHUT UP.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[URINATING]
[URINATING STOPS]
- GRAB THIS SHIT.
- SHIT.
DON'T TAKE IT YET.
WHERE'D YOU
GET THIS SHIT?
I ALWAYS HAVE
A SECRET STASH.
WHY YOU BEEN
HOLDING OUT?
BECAUSE WE HANG AROUND
A BUNCH OF FUCKING SCAVENGERS,
- THAT'S WHY.
- LET'S SHOOT THIS SHIT, COME ON.
AH!
- [GROANS]
- SON OF A BITCH!
THIS IS FROM
MY FUCKING STASH.
- YOU'RE THE FUCKING SCAVENGER.
- BOYS, BOYS, BOYS!
- YES IT IS.
- I PRESENT TO YOU THE BEGINNING...
OF BRIAN'S BITCHING BREW.
THIS SHIT LOOKS OFF.
TRUST ME,
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL.
TO THE BEGINNING!
[BRIAN GIGGLES]
[SNICKERS]
KNEW THAT SHIT
DIDN'T LOOK RIGHT.
IT'S POTENT, THOUGH.
THAT'S LIKE OVER 14%.
THIS SHIT IS WORSE
THAN I THOUGHT.
BUT... IT'LL DO
THE FUCKING TRICK.
- [CHUCKLES]
- 14%,
THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT
DID I HIT YOU?
OH, SHIT, WE'RE OUT.
MOVE!
[RETCHES]
[MAN]
WHAT THE FUCK, BRO?
[JADE]
VICTOR, ARE YOU OKAY?
HELL YEAH!
[LAUGHS]
OUT WITH THE OLD
AND IN WITH THE NEW!
[CHEERING]
GET THIS MOTHERFUCKER
A BEER
- RIGHT HERE.
- YEAH!
[LAUGHS]
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ GONNA GET YOU HIGH ♪
♪ WONDERING WHAT YOU GOT ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY... ♪
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[FUSE HISSING]
FIRE IN THE HOLE, BITCHES.
YOU BETTER RUN,
MOTHERFUCKERS!
[LAUGHS]
OH, SHIT.
OH, SHIT, OH, SHIT.
- [EXCITED LAUGHING]
- OH, SHIT.
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
[LAUGHTER]
- I GOT YOU, BITCH!
- [SQUEALS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC PLAYING
OVER STEREO]
[ROME MOANING]
DUDE, THIS PARTY'S
DEAD, MAN.
[ROME GIGGLING
AND MOANING]
[EXHALES]
YOU TRYING
TO GET OUT OF HERE?
DUDE, DON'T OVERDO IT, MAN,
I ONLY GOT A COUPLE CANS.
EVERY TIME I GO
AND GET MORE,
THEY GIVE ME
A HARD-ASS FUCKING TIME.
WHAT KIND OF COUNTRY
HAS A LAW AGAINST
HOW MUCH FUCKING PAINT
YOU CAN BUY?
MAN, THEY GOT LAWS
FOR EVERYTHING.
FOR THE LAND
OF THE FREE,
YOU GOT TO FOLLOW A LOT
OF FUCKING RULES.
HEY, YO, DUDE, DUDE,
HEADLIGHTS, HEADLIGHTS, CHILL.
FUCK IT!
[ENGINE REVS, TIRES SCREECH,
SIREN WAILING]
SHIT! FUCK! COPS, COPS!
[KING]
AW!
FUCK!
[SIREN CHIRPING, WAILING]
COME ON!
[KING]
JUST GOT TO OUTRUN YOUR ASS.
[PANTING]
[EXCLAIMS]
HOLY SHIT!
I THINK WE DID IT, BRO!
[LAUGHS]
AH!
[KING GROANS, SQUEALS]
[LAUGHS]
FUCK!
[BOTH PANTING]
HEY, WHERE DID
YOU GUYS GO?
- [LAUGHS]
- DUDE, IS THE FRONT DOOR LOCKED?
- THE FUCKING COPS ARE AFTER US, MAN.
- FUCK!
- I DON'T KNOW, I'LL CHECK.
- WHAT THE FUCK, Y'ALL?
- WHAT ABOUT COPS?
- GET THE FUCK OFF HIM, BRO.
DID THEY SEE
YOU COME HERE?
I DON'T KNOW, MAN, THEY WERE
RIGHT THE FUCK ON TOP OF US.
FUCK! THEN WHY
DID YOU COME HERE?
CHILL!
WILL ONE OF YOU
SHUT THE FUCK UP?
- DAMN.
- [POUNDING ON DOOR]
FUCK. THEY'RE RIGHT
THE FUCK OUTSIDE.
THIS IS THE APD,
WE KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE!
IF YOU DO NOT LET US IN,
WE WILL HAVE TO FORCE ENTRY!
I REPEAT, WE WILL
- FORCE ENTRY!
- THEY'RE THE FUCK OUTSIDE.
YOU'RE FUCKING STUPID!
WHY WOULD YOU BRING COPS HERE?
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT,
PLEASE SHUT UP!
- DAMN IT!
- WHAT THE FUCK, BRO?
GET HER THE FUCK
OFF ME, MAN.
- GET HER THE FUCK OFF ME!
- CHILL, CHILL, CHILL!
- STOP!
- [OFFICER 2] UNIT BASE,
WE HAVE THE PERPETRATORS
AT 313 WEST 8TH STREET.
REQUEST ADDITIONAL BACK-UP,
ALSO REQUEST PERMISSION
TO FORCE ENTRY, OVER.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[RADIO BEEPS]
[BRIAN]
STOP.
- IT'S ALREADY TOO LATE.
- [KING] LATE FOR WHAT?
- HEY, HEY, HEY.
- HOLY SHIT, DAWG.
[KING]
HEY, WE WERE JUST TAGGING, BRO.
[ALL CLAMORING]
- YEAH, YEAH, SURE.
- CAUGHT RED-HANDED!
- FUCK YOU! FUCK YOU!
- CAUGHT RED-HANDED! CAUGHT RED-HANDED!
- SHUT THE FUCK UP, KING.
- CHILL, CHILL OUT.
JOHN, SHUT
THE FUCK UP, DAWG.
THERE'S LIKE
SEVEN COPS OUT THERE.
YO, I DON'T GIVE A FUCK!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
HEY, LISTEN UP.
SHIT.
YOU OPEN THIS DOOR,
NOBODY GOES TO JAIL.
IF YOU DON'T OPEN THIS DOOR,
EVERYBODY'S GOING TO FUCKING JAIL!
- YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
- SHH. SHH. SHH.
- THERE'S NO POINT IN CLEANING UP!
- HEY!
WE JUST NEED TO ACT
LIKE NO ONE'S HERE.
- WE WAIT 'EM OUT, WE WAIT 'EM OUT.
- YEAH, DAWG. HEY...
THEY NEED A FUCKING WARRANT
TO COME IN HERE ANYWAYS.
Y'ALL KNOW THAT.
CHECK THIS OUT.
- [ALL CLAMORING]
- CHILL THE FUCK OUT, ALL RIGHT?
YOU ARE SUCH
A FUCKING IDIOT, DUDE.
SHUT THE FUCK UP, BRO!
WHAT, YOU GONNA
CHARGE UP ON ME, DAWG?
THIS IS GONNA BE FUN.
[LAUGHS]
- JUST CHILL THE FUCK OUT...
- SHOW US A FUCKING WARRANT.
SHOW US A FUCKING WARRANT!
WE'RE JUST HERE
FOR TWO MEN!
GIVE THEM UP AND YOU CAN
GO ON ABOUT YOUR NIGHT.
SOME BULLSHIT.
COPS ARE SUCH ASSHOLES.
GODDAMN IT!
LOOK, LOOK, LOOK,
WE'LL JUST SIT HERE,
WE'LL WAIT 'EM OUT, WE MAKE 'EM GO
THROUGH THE PROCESS, ALL RIGHT?
IT'S LIKE 4 A.M.,
IT'LL TAKE 'EM FOREVER
TO GET A WARRANT.
NOBODY OPENS THAT DOOR.
CUT THE POWER.
GRAB THUMPER.
SHOW THESE MOTHERFUCKERS
WHAT'S UP.
FUCK THIS,
I'M THROWING KING'S ASS.
- I'M NOT GOING TO FUCKING JAIL!
- GET THE FUCK OFF ME, MAN!
- SHUT THE FUCK UP, MAN.
- GET THE FUCK OFF OF ME!
WILL YOU SHUT
THE FUCK UP, FOOL?
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
YO, YO.
I THINK
THEY'RE LEAVING, DAWG.
YEAH, YEAH.
- THEY'RE LEAVING, DAWG
- HELL YEAH!
I TOLD YOU ASSHOLES.
THEY ALWAYS FUCKING LEAVE, MAN.
- FUCKING HATERS!
- SHUT THE FUCK UP, MAN.
- THEY WOULDN'T JUST LEAVE.
THAT'S WEIRD, MAN.
[MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY]
- OH, SHIT.
- DUDE...
DUDE, I THINK
THEY CUT THE POWER.
NO SHIT,
YOU FUCKING IDIOT.
- MM.
- [KING] SHUT THE FUCK UP, BRO.
[LAUGHS]
[ELECTRICITY HUMMING]
WHAT'S UP WITH
THE POWER, DUDE?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- [OFFICER 1] ON THE GROUND!
- [OFFICER 2] FREEZE!
HEAD DOWN!
HANDS UP IN THE AIR! NOW!
YOU, GET DOWN, NOW!
- STOP MOVING! YOU HEAR ME?
- FREEZE!
- ON THE GROUND NOW!
- DON'T MOVE!
- STOP RIGHT THERE!
- HALT! DOWN ON THE GROUND!
GET DOWN!
- GET ON THE GROUND!
- NOW!
FREEZE!
ON THE GROUND, NOW!
STOP! FREEZE!
[KING] GET THE FUCK OFF OF ME!
BITCH! BITCH!
[SIREN CHIRPING]
FALL ON THE GROUND!
GET ON THE GROUND NOW!
GET THE FUCK
OFF ME, FUCKER!
- STOP! STOP RESISTING!
- I'M NOT!
HANDS BEHIND YOUR BACK!
FUCKING PIG!
GET THE FUCK OFF ME!
SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
I'M NOT YOUR
FUCKING KID, BITCH!
FUCK YOU, MAN.
- FUCK YOU!
- [HANDCUFFS CLICKING]
THIS IS EVERY DAY
FOR ME, BITCH!
- GET THE FUCK OFF ME!
- CALM DOWN, HUH?
GET THE FUCK OFF ME!
[CLAMORING]
- [SCREAMING]
- YEAH, NOT SO BIG NOW,
ARE YOU, PUNK?
GET THE FUCK UP.
[SCREAMING, CLAMORING]
- GET IN THE CHAIR.
- FUCK YOU!
- NOW!
- FUCK!
GET 'EM ON THE WALL!
GET 'EM!
HANDS BEHIND YOUR BACK!
COME OVER HERE.
- FUCK YOU! FUCK!
- NOW.
[JASON]
FUCK YOU, BITCH!
GET YOUR HANDS
BEHIND YOUR BACK.
HANDS BEHIND YOUR BACK.
YOU'RE A BITCH
MOTHERFUCKER, DAWG.
[OLES] YOU THINK THEY GIVE
OUT A FUCKING MEDAL FOR...?
[KING]
FUCK YOU!
[CLAMORING, YELLING]
GET THE FUCK OFF ME! I DIDN'T
FUCKING DO NOTHING, MAN.
TAKE THAT FUCKING BADGE OFF AND
SAY THAT SHIT, MOTHERFUCKER.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO NOW, PUNK BITCH?
TAKE THAT FUCKING BADGE OFF
AND SAY IT!
I DIDN'T DO SHIT!
[BRIAN] WE DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING, WE HAVE RIGHTS!
YOU LOST YOUR RIGHTS
WHEN YOU DIDN'T LET US IN.
WE DIDN'T FUCKING
DO ANYTHING!
WE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
SHOW ME THE FUCKING WARRANT!
JUDGING BY THE LOOKS
OF THIS PLACE,
I'M SURE ALL OF Y'ALL
ARE GUILTY OF PLENTY.
FUCK YOU.
SIT STILL,
YOU LITTLE SHIT.
SPREAD 'EM, SWEETHEART.
THIS IS NOT A GAME.
GET YOUR FUCKING
HANDS OFF ME.
LEAVE HER ALONE, YOU FUCK!
SHE'S A FUCKING GIRL!
- I SAID SHUT THE FUCK UP!
- FUCK YOU!
[BRIAN GROANS]
ON YOUR FUCKING KNEES!
LOOKS LIKE Y'ALL ARE A BUNCH OF
REAL WINNERS HERE.
[CHUCKLES]
[BRIAN]
FUCK YOU!
WE DIDN'T FUCKING
DO ANYTHING!
GET THAT THE FUCK
OFF HER!
FUCK YOU, PIG!
I'M SURE
YOUR DADDY'S PROUD.
GET THE FUCK
OFF OF HER!
WE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
FUCK YOU!
OW! FUCK YOU!
YOU NEED TO LEARN
TO SHUT YOUR FUCKING MOUTH.
FUCK YOU!
YOU WANT TO DIE TONIGHT,
MOTHERFUCKER?
GET THE FUCK OUT.
[GROANING, SCREAMING]
GIVE HIM HELP ON THE WALL,
GIVE HIM HELP ON THE WALL.
FUCK!
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE,
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[CLAMORING]
- CALM THE FUCK DOWN!
- WHAT'S UP, DAWG?
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.
THOUGHT YOU SAID WE DIDN'T HAVE
ANY FUCKING RIGHTS?
YOU GOT QUITE A FUCKING
MOUTH ON YOU, BOY.
- FUCK YOU!
- FUCK ME?
FUCK YOU, MOTHERFUCKER.
- AH, FUCK!
- COME ON.
HOW'S THAT FEEL, BITCH?
[BRIAN GROANS]
[OFFICER]
CALM DOWN! STOP RESISTING!
[BRIAN]
FUCK! FUCK!
[RADIO CHATTER,
BRIAN COUGHING, SPITTING]
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
[CLAMORING CONTINUING
OUTSIDE]
- HEY!
- YOU GOT ANY DRUGS? WHERE THE DRUGS AT?
THE FUCK YOU'D SAY,
MOTHERFUCKER?
[YELLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAMERON]
I HAVE IN MY HAND
MULTIPLE
POLICE REPORTS FILED
OVER THE LAST
FOUR YEARS.
ALL OF THESE REPORTS
TOOK PLACE
AT THE SAME ESTABLISHMENT
YOU FREQUENTED.
UNDERAGE DRINKING,
MULTIPLE ACCOUNTS
OF EXCESSIVE NOISE,
MULTIPLE ARRESTS, INCLUDING
MINORS IN POSSESSION OF ALCOHOL,
MINORS IN CONSUMPTION
OF ALCOHOL,
PUBLIC INTOXICATION,
DRUG PARAPHERNALIA,
RESISTING ARREST,
AND ASSAULT OF
A POLICE OFFICER.
DO YOU WISH TO DENY ANY OF
THESE TRUTHS, MISS HENDRICKS?
OR DO YOU BELIEVE THAT
ENDING UP BEHIND BARS
IS ALL A MATTER
OF CIRCUMSTANCE?
[PUPPY YOWLS]
[BRIAN LAUGHS]
[JADE]
THEY'RE SO FAT!
[BRIAN CHUCKLES]
[JADE]
LOOK AT HIM!
AW, I WANT THEM ALL!
THIS GUY.
HE'S, LIKE, PASSED OUT.
- [LAUGHS]
- OH, HEY!
OH, NO.
[JADE]
OH, MY GOD.
I WANT HIM.
- [BRIAN] I WANT ALL OF THEM.
- [JADE] OH.
HEY, HEY, BUDDY.
HE'S SO LITTLE.
[PUPPY BARKING]
- HEY! HEY.
- YEAH.
[BRIAN]
COME HERE, BUD.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL,
LITTLE BUDDY.
IT'S NO FUN BEING
LOCKED IN A CAGE.
- [PUPPY BARKS]
- [BOTH LAUGH]
[BARKING]
OH, SWEETIE.
GONNA BE LIKE SIMBA.
[BOTH LAUGH]
WHAT ABOUT "PISTOL"?
WHAT ABOUT "SHOTGUN"?
- MM...
- [PUPPY WHINES]
NO, NONE OF THOSE.
- HE DOESN'T LIKE 'EM?
- UH-UH.
OH.
[JADE]
HEY.
WHAT IS THIS,
"DESTROY EVERYTHING"?
FILTH.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
YOU...
- FILTH.
- MM-MM.
BLATZ. SHIT SPLIT.
DOUBLE CD?
ARE YOU FUCKING KIDDING ME?
I'M SORRY,
I DON'T KNOW ANY OF THOSE.
OH, MY GOD, I FEEL LIKE
I FAILED YOU!
IT HURTS ME ON THE INSIDE THAT
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
LIKE...
- HELL NO.
- [PUPPY WHIMPERING]
THE ONLY THING THAT YOU
FAILED AT IS NAMING A PUPPY.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GIVE IT A GO.
GIVE ME HIM.
HI, PUPPY.
[IMITATES SOFT BARKING]
SO WHO THE FUCK
IS FILTH ANYWAY?
IT'S THE GREATEST FUCKING
BAND IN THE WORLD.
COME HERE.
MM, I'M NOT
AFRAID OF YOU.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[JADE]
HMM.
WHAT ABOUT "GUINNESS"?
I KIND OF
FUCKING LOVE THAT.
EXCEPT I HATE IT
'CAUSE YOU CAME UP WITH IT.
- SO... [CHUCKLES]
- AH!
ALL RIGHT, WAIT,
BUT WE COULD STILL
NAME HIM AFTER
THE BEST BEER EVER.
WHAT ABOUT "STOUT"?
- HE KIND OF LOOKS LIKE A STOUT.
- YEAH.
YOU LIKE THAT, BUDDY?
YOU WANT TO BE
NAMED "STOUT"?
- A-HA-HA.
- "STOUT" IT IS.
- I LIKE IT.
- PERFECT.
PERFECT. STOUT.
I LOVE IT.
- HEY, WHAT'S THIS?
- HEY!
DUDE... IT'S NOTHING,
I JUST KEEP LYRICS
TO SONGS IN IT AND STUFF
AND JUST THINGS I LIKE
AND RANDOM THOUGHTS I HAVE.
SO IT'S LIKE
A FUCKING DIARY.
- IT'S NOT A FUCKING DIARY!
- [LAUGHS]
IT'S JUST FUCKING
LYRICS AND...
RANDOM IDEAS AND...
FUCKING GIVE IT BACK!
I'LL GIVE IT BACK
ON ONE CONDITION:
YOU READ ME SOMETHING
WRITTEN BY YOU
AND NOT ANOTHER BAND.
IT'S EITHER THAT
OR YOU NEVER GET IT BACK.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
JUST GIVE IT HERE.
YOU HAVE TO PROMISE.
YOU HAVE TO SAY IT.
I THOUGHT YOU DIDN'T
LIKE PROMISES.
SO?
[CHUCKLES]
ALL RIGHT, I PROMISE.
BUT, LIKE...
YOU GOT TO REALIZE THAT...
I HEAR THIS TO
REALLY LOUD MUSIC,
AND LIKE...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
HERE, LET ME SEE THAT.
[GASPS]
JUST...
IN MY HEAD,
IT'S MOSTLY SCREAMING.
MM-HMM.
[BRIAN SIGHS]
ALL RIGHT, YOU READY?
YEAH, GO AHEAD.
"MY ENTIRE LIFE,
PEOPLE TRY TO
RATTLE MY CAGE
TO FORCE ME TO EXPLODE
FROM THE INSIDE OUT.
TESTING ME.
TRYING TO FIND
MY BREAKING POINT.
MY MOTHER WOULD SAY,
'SON, STEP IN FROM THE COLD, '
AND MY FATHER
JUST THE SAME.
HE'D SAY,
'DON'T EVER LOSE
YOUR SELF-CONTROL.'
BUT I OPENED THE WINDOW.
I LET THE COLD AIR FLOW.
I LOST MY SELF-CONTROL."
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- MM.
- [CHUCKLING]
[CAMERON]
CODY CATES LIVED AN HONEST LIFE.
MWAH!
[CAMERON]
WENT TO CHURCH EVERY SUNDAY.
PLAYED FOOTBALL.
HE ALSO WAS INVOLVED
IN MANY OTHER
EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES:
NATIONAL HONORS SOCIETY,
STUDENT COUNCIL,
FELLOWSHIP OF
CHRISTIAN ATHLETES.
HIS FAMILY
HAVE ALWAYS BEEN PROACTIVE
IN THE COMMUNITY.
IS THIS WHAT
THEY DESERVE?
THEY DIDN'T ASK FOR
ANY OF THIS TO HAPPEN.
SO IS THIS
WHAT THEY
REALLY DESERVE?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ L-I-S-E-O ♪
♪ RIDE HARD, NIGGA ♪
♪ AY ♪
♪ I'M GON' SCRATCH
UNTIL I GET IT, GO AT IT ♪
♪ COME BACK WITH IT ♪
♪ I'M GON' SCRATCH
UNTIL I GET IT ♪
♪ GO AT IT,
COME BACK WITH IT ♪
♪ I'M GON' SCRATCH
UNTIL I GET IT ♪
♪ GO AT IT,
COME BACK WITH IT ♪
♪ I'M GON' SCRATCH
UNTIL I GET IT ♪
♪ GO AT IT,
COME BACK WITH IT ♪
♪ YOUNG NIGGA
ON THE GRIND ♪
[CHEERING]
♪ YOUNG NIGGA
ON THE GRIND ♪
♪ AND I THROW IT IN THE GAME,
NIGGAS MAD ♪
♪ BITCHES HATIN',
KEEPING DIRT ON MY NAME ♪
♪ NIGGAS STARE
AS I SWING ♪
♪ SEE, THEY SLIP
INTO FRAME ♪
♪ TRUE BANK,
USED TO BANG ♪
♪ MONEY RUNNING
THROUGH MY NAME ♪
[CODY] LIKE, WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS
NOW THAT THE CHEER SEASON'S OVER?
CHEER SEASON
DOESN'T END WITH FOOTBALL.
- THERE ARE OTHER SPORTS.
- YEAH.
YEAH, I MEAN, LIKE...
I MEANT, LIKE, ARE YOU
BUMMED NOW THAT THE...
- THE FOOTBALL SEASON'S OVER?
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
HONESTLY,
IT'S KIND OF EXHAUSTING.
YOU KNOW,
ALL THE PEP RALLIES
AND STUPID
SIGN MAKING
AND STUFF.
HEY, THIS PARTY'S GETTING
A LITTLE OUT OF CONTROL.
DO YOU GUYS THINK
THE COPS WILL COME?
NO, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
I TOLD YOU,
COPS NEVER COME.
YEAH, I MEAN, COPS?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
YO, WE RUN THIS TOWN.
RUN THIS TOWN,
BITCHES! OOH-HOO!
[CHEERING, LAUGHING]
[SNIFFS]
OH, SHIT, MAN!
[PANTS]
- HOW YOU DOING?
- GOOD.
- OH, SHIT! I ALMOST FORGOT TO SHOW YOU ALL
MY LATEST AND GREATEST.
IF, UM... YOU'D ALL PLEASE
ACCOMPANY ME TO MY RIDE.
OKAY.
[CHUCKLES]
PEACE.
[GIGGLES]
RICKY.
GOT TO BE MORE LIKE HIM,
YOU KNOW?
RICKY:
I... THIS
THIS IS
THE GREATEST INVENTION
SINCE GODDAMN... COKE.
VICKS... COME ON.
- STEP ON UP HERE.
- ARE YOU SHIT-FACED, MAN?
- I'M CATES, BABY.
- COME ON! CATES.
FUCK, I'M DRUNKER
THAN A SKUNK.
GET UP THERE, MOTHERFUCKER.
COME ON.
COME ON, PUT YOUR MOUTH
UP ON THAT THING.
NO, MAN, WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS THING,
- YOU CRAZY-ASS REDNECK?
- QUIT...
BEING SUCH
A GODDAMN PUSS.
JUST...
PUT YOUR MOUTH
ON THE FUCKING THING.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING.
YEAH?
YOU'RE RUINING
MY GODDAMN PRESENTATION.
ALL RIGHT.
[PANTS EXCITEDLY]
WHOO-HOO!
[CHEERING, LAUGHTER]
[SPITS]
OOH, GOD!
MAN, WHAT THE HELL?
IS THAT FUCKING WHISKEY?
GODDAMN RIGHT
IT'S WHISKEY!
I MEAN, THAT IS
THE BEST FUCKING SHIT
IN THE GODDAMN WORLD
WHISKEY, OKAY?
IT'S NOT CHEAP,
IT'S FUCKING EXPENSIVE STUFF
SO BE GODDAMN
APPRECIATIVE, OKAY?
- [COUGHS]
- NOW, SEE, I RIGGED THE WINDSHIELD WIPER
TO FLOW WHISKEY STRAIGHT
INTO YOUR FUCKING MOUTH.
AND YOU'RE SO UNAPPRECIATIVE,
YOU LITTLE COCK SUCKER.
[RICKY EXHALES]
DAVIS, GET YOUR ASS
ON UP HERE.
- NO, NO, BRO, I'M GOOD.
- NO, YEAH, COME ON.
NO, SCREW YOU, DAWG.
[CODY] NO, YOUR FOOTBALL
CAREER JUST ENDED.
YOU'RE OFFICIALLY RETIRED,
ALL WASHED UP.
- COME ON, MAN.
- RICKY: CATES!
DROP YOUR COCK,
AND PUT ON YOUR SOCK.
ENJOY THE FUCKING WHISKEY,
PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[MAN]
COME ON! COME ON!
[RICKY GIGGLES]
UGH!
[LAUGHTER]
[COUGHS]
HEY, HOW'S IT FEEL?
- LIKE SHIT.
- WE'RE NOT ALONE.
[TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
[MUSIC STOPS]
ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL,
TIME TO BREAK IT UP.
COME ON.
PARTY'S OVER.
GET HOME SAFE.
YO, RICKY.
- YEAH?
- WHERE Y'ALL HEADED?
YEAH, BUDDY.
[CHUCKLES]
THANK YOU.
[DAVIS]
TELL THE KIDS I SAID HI.
MUCH OBLIGED, Y'ALL.
[DAVIS]
LATER, BUDDY.
HEY, CODY, CAN WE GIVE
LINDSEY A RIDE HOME?
UH, HELL YEAH WE CAN.
[CHUCKLES]
THANKS.
[RICKY]
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET THE FUCK
OUT OF HERE.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[MUSIC PLAYING
OVER CAR STEREO]
THANKS AGAIN, GUYS,
I APPRECIATE IT.
ALL RIGHT,
Y'ALL BE SAFE.
♪ I'M A SOLDIER,
I'M A GANGSTA, NIGGA ♪
♪ GHETTO BOY
ON MY BELLY ♪
[DAVIS]
HURRY THE FUCK UP, RICKY!
OH, MY GOD.
OH, SHIT.
- [CHUCKLES]
- DAMN.
♪ GIVE A FUCK WHO YOU ARE ♪
♪ I'M A BEAST,
I'M A REAL STREET NIGGA ♪
♪ LEAD A OTHER NEW WAY ♪
- ♪ GOT A GANG OF THEM KILLERS ♪
- ♪ WITH ME ♪
♪ DON'T GET IT TWISTED,
I'M THE ONE, THE DADDY ♪
♪ I'M THE SHEPHERD... ♪
[MAN AND WOMAN
MOANING ON TV]
[MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
WHAT THE FUCK, MAN?
[EXHALES]
OH, YOU FUCKING BITCH!
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- WHOO-HOO!
UGH! YOU MOTHERFUCKER!
- FUCK YOU, PUSSY!
- FUCK!
FUCKING BITCH-ASS FUCKER.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[RICKY] WE WERE MINDING
OUR OWN BUSINESS.
OKAY?
[SCOFFING]
IT WAS AN ALL-OUT AMBUSH.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHEERING, CLAPPING]
- WELCOME TO THE PARTY, MY MAN.
- HOW YOU FUCKING BITCHES DOING?
[CHEERS]
[MAN]
YEAH, WE'RE GETTING FUCKED UP.
[RICKY]
LOOK AT THIS DUMB PIECE OF SHIT.
WHICH ONE OF YOU MOTHERFUCKERS
BROKE MY WINDOW?
EXCUSE ME, FAGGOT?
[YELLING]
I SAID,
WHICH ON OF YOU
MOTHERFUCKERS
BROKE MY FUCKING WINDOW?
DO YOU KISS YOUR BOYFRIEND
WITH THAT FUCKING MOUTH?
[RICKY GROANS]
[MAN]
GET HIM! GET HIM!
[RICKY]
GET THAT MOTHERFUCKER!
[KING]
AH!
[RICKY]
GET THAT MOTHERFUCKER!
- [CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
- GET HIM!
- GET OFF ME!
[CLAMORING, CHEERING]
SETTLE DOWN,
SETTLE DOWN.
COME ON,
MOTHERFUCKER.
GET UP. COME ON, BOY.
GET OFF ME, MAN.
NOW LISTEN,
I'D ADMIRE YOUR SPIRIT,
I REALLY DO.
BUT YOU DONE... FUCKED...
UP...
REAL... FUCKING...
BAD! HUH?
- HEY. HEY, YOU...
- [SPITS]
BITCH!
- [GRUNTS]
- AH!
SORRY I DROPPED
MY FUCKING CHAIN ON YOUR FACE.
- GET HIM!
- [CHEERING, CLAMORING]
GET THE FUCK OFF ME, MAN!
GET THE FUCK OFF ME!
GET THE FUCK
OFF ME!
[MAN]
GET UP!
[BELLOWS]
I WILL NOT STOP
TILL EVERY
LAST ONE OF YOU
MOTHERFUCKERS
IS SIX FEET
THE FUCK UNDER!
[BELLOWS]
WRATH IS ON,
MOTHERFUCKERS!
Y'ALL BETTER PRAY!
[CLAMORING]
[WHOOPING GROWING LOUDER]
FUCK!
[MUFFLED CHEERING, WHOOPING]
[MUSIC PLAYING
OVER STEREO]
[VOMITS]
[MUSIC VOLUME TURNED UP]
[YELLS]
♪ AND THE ASHTRAY'S
JUST A PETTING ZOO ♪
♪ BUT WE'RE NOT GONNA
PISS IN A CUP ♪
♪ NO, WE'RE GONNA
FUCK SHIT UP! ♪
[WHOOPING GROWING LOUDER]
[MUSIC PLAYING
ON CAR STEREO]
[LAUGHTER]
[OLES AS ARNOLD SCHWARZENEGGER]
LISTEN TO ME,
I KNOW HE CAN'T HEAR US.
[MUSIC PLAYING
OVER CAR STEREO]
♪ WHAT'S YOUR REASON ♪
♪ FOR EXISTENCE? ♪
♪ DO YOU BELIEVE
IN ANYTHING? ♪
♪ OR DOES YOUR LIFESTYLE... ♪
[TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
- DAMN.
- WHAT THE FUCK, Y'ALL?
[BRIAN]
WHAT THE FUCK?
ISN'T THAT
ONE OF YOURS?
[BRIAN] LOOKS LIKE IT
WENT WAY PAST WORDS.
[JASON] FUCK THIS, DUDE,
WE NEED TO HANDLE SHIT.
COME ON, DUDE.
LET ME SEE STOUT. I DON'T WANT
ANY GLASS TO GET IN HIS PAWS.
- [CHUCKLES]
- MM.
I'M GONNA SET UP,
LIKE, A LITTLE...
- HOUSE FOR HIM.
- AW.
I'LL MAKE HIM
A BREWERY.
STOUT'S BREWERY.
[STRAINING]
DAMN, THIS FUCKER'S HEAVY.
[GRUNTS]
ONE, TWO, THREE.
[BRIAN]
THERE WE GO.
GIMME, GIMME, GIMME.
OKAY.
- BE CAREFUL.
- OKAY.
HEY, BUDDY.
- AW.
- HEY, BUDDY.
HERE, LET ME
GET HIM SOME FOOD.
[CHUCKLES]
YOU OKAY?
YOU LIKE YOUR NEW HOUSE?
[METAL CLANGS]
[BAG RUSTLING]
HUNGRY?
YOU HUNGRY, BUDDY?
THIS IS FUCKING BULLSHIT.
YO, HELP ME PATCH
THIS UP REAL QUICK.
MIGHT BE SOME NAILS
LYING ALL AROUND.
- [BRIAN] YOU GOT IT?
- [JASON] YEAH, YEAH, I GOT IT.
LET ME GET
THE OTHER SIDE.
HOLD IT UP.
I'M HOLDING IT, DAWG.
THE FUCK?
[CAR APPROACHING]
[TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
[JASON] NO, JUST LEAVE IT.
IT'S GOOD.
[BRIAN]
YO, WHERE'S THE CAR AT?
- [JASON] OH, WHAT THE FUCK HAPPENED TO YOUR FACE, BRO?
- [OLES] HOLY SHIT.
JOHN...
- KING!
WHAT THE FUCK, DUDE?
DUDE!
WHAT THE FUCK HAPPENED, MAN?
IT'S ALL RIGHT, DUDE.
YOU CAN TELL ME.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I'VE HAD ENOUGH, MAN.
I'M TIRED.
I'M TIRED OF...
SITTING AROUND AND...
LETTING THEM ACT LIKE
WE DON'T HAVE A PLACE.
SO I WENT DOWN THERE
TO SHOW THEM
THAT WE AREN'T GONNA SIT AROUND
AND TAKE ANYMORE OF THEIR SHIT.
LET'S EVEN
THE MOTHERFUCKING ODDS.
I GOT A BAD FUCKING
FEELING ABOUT THIS, MAN.
SHUT THE FUCK UP.
YO!
YO! SHIT'S GONE ON
TOO FAR, MAN.
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
YOU SAID SO YOURSELF,
- WE HAVE TO MAKE A FUCKING STATEMENT.
- [OLES] YEAH, DAWG.
WE CAN'T JUST SIT HERE AND ACT LIKE
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BLOW THE FUCK OVER.
- IT AIN'T GONNA STOP EITHER.
- NEXT TIME, IT COULD BE YOU,
ME, YOUR GIRL
OR ANY FUCKING ONE OF US.
I'M GOING WITH
OR WITHOUT YOU.
HE'S RIGHT, MAN.
SHIT'S GONE ON
WAY TOO FUCKING LONG.
YOU DON'T FUCKING KNOW, THERE COULD
BE, LIKE, A SHITLOAD OF THEM.
THEN WE FUCKING
EQUALIZE IT!
- YEAH, FUCKING EQUALIZERS.
- Y'ALL NEED TO CALM THE FUCK DOWN.
FUCK THIS.
- BRIAN!
- WHAT?
LOOK AT THIS
FUCKING PLACE!
LOOK AT KING'S
FUCKING FACE!
- LET'S FUCKING DO THIS, YO.
- LET'S GO. CRASS, COME ON.
- HEY, WAIT!
- WHAT?
I'M SORRY.
WE NEED TO BE
IN THIS TOGETHER.
ALL RIGHT?
WE'LL BE FINE.
COME ON.
- [ENGINE STARTS]
- [OLES] LET'S ROLL!
COME ON, BRIAN!
WHOO!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
LET'S FUCKING DO THIS!
[KING]
LET'S GO!
[OLES]
COME ON, MOTHERFUCKERS!
WHOO!
GO, GO, GO, GO!
[EXHALES SHAKILY]
I DON'T REMEMBER.
EVENTS OF THAT NIGHT
ARE BLANK.
ARE THEY BLANK 'CAUSE YOU HAD A
COUPLE OF DRINKS TO EASE YOUR NERVES?
[OVER CAR STEREO] ♪ OR DOES
YOUR LIFESTYLE CONTRADICT ♪
♪ THE WORDS YOU WRITE
FOR THE SONGS YOU SING? ♪
♪ SING ♪
♪ SING, SING ♪
♪ GET YOUR FREAK ON ♪
I MEAN,
THEY WERE EVERYWHERE.
THEY WERE...
HAD WEAPONS,
HAD ALL KINDS OF BATS.
I MEAN, WE WEREN'T
EXPECTING THAT.
[STAMMERING]
WE DIDN'T COME FOR THAT.
I FEEL LIKE...
IT WAS ALL MY FAULT.
[LAUGHTER,
INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- FUCKERS, COME ON!
- [WHOOPING]
YOU KNOW, IT'S A FUCKING
PAIN IN THE ASS
EVERY TWO WEEKS TO HAVE TO
BEAT ONE OF THESE FUCKERS DOWN.
[YELLING]
RIGHT? AM I FUCKING RIGHT?
[CHEERING IN AGREEMENT]
[PUNK MUSIC BLARING
OVER CAR STEREO]
[DAVIS]
THE STUFF I RECALL IS
PRETTY HARD TO FORGET.
AND AT THAT POINT,
IT HAD BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I HAD ANYTHING TO DRINK.
- BYE!
- BYE.
IT'S GOOD SEEING YOU.
HAVE A GOOD ONE.
[DAVIS]
YO, LET'S GET UP THERE.
RICKY KEEPS
BLOWING ME UP.
[PUNK MUSIC BLARING
OVER CAR STEREO]
[MICHELLE] THESE FIGHTS
NEVER WOULD MATERIALIZE.
ONE SIDE WOULD SHOW UP
AND EVERYONE WOULD
GATHER IN THE PARKING LOT
LIKE A BIG, FUN
SOCIAL EVENT.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT
WAS GOING TO HAPPEN.
BUT NO ONE
WAS READY FOR THIS.
[CLAMORING, GLASS SHATTERS]
[SNIFFLES, SIGHS]
I WANTED TO SAY SOMETHING,
BUT IT WAS TOO LATE.
I WISH...
[INHALES DEEPLY]
IT WAS JUST TOO LATE.
[TEENAGERS CLAMORING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
- BOOM! BOOM! BOOM!
- WHOO-HOO!
FUCKER, COME HERE!
COME HERE!
COME HERE,
YOU FUCKERS!
IT'S NOW OR NEVER,
MOTHERFUCKERS!
WE END THIS SHIT TONIGHT.
RICKY: COME HERE. COME
HERE, MOTHERFUCKER
COME ON.
- YO, WHAT THE FUCK IS GOING ON?
- YEAH, LET'S JUST GET OUT OF HERE.
- FUCK!
- DAVIS, DAVIS, CAN WE PLEASE GET OUT OF HERE?
YO, JUST SHUT THE FUCK UP,
ALL RIGHT?
- LET ME THINK!
- NO, FUCK THAT, WE NEED TO DO SOMETHING.
WE'RE FUCKED UP! WAIT!
[PANTING]
[CHUCKLES]
I'M A NINJA IN MY CADDY.
[MICHELLE] WAIT, CODY, STOP THIS!
STOP IT, WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE!
SHUT UP, NO. PLEASE,
CAN WE JUST GET OUT OF HERE?
[ENGINE REVVING]
- OH, MY GOD!
- OH!
- WHOO!
- [MICHELLE EXCLAIMS]
OH, MY GOSH, WHAT...
- [DAVIS] FUCK!
- [MICHELLE] WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STOP IT, MAN, LET ME OUT
OF THIS FUCKING CAR!
- HOLY SHIT!
- ALL RIGHT!
NO, WE'RE FUCKING GOING.
[EXHALES]
[CLAMORING]
[KING SCREAMING]
- [EXHALES]
- [DAVIS] GET THE FUCK OUT OF THE WAY.
[EXCLAIMS]
W-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET ME THE FUCK
OUT OF THIS CAR.
[GRUNTING]
[MICHELLE]
NO!
W-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CODY, STOP THIS! STOP IT,
- WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE!
- [DAVIS] STOP!
- [MICHELLE] OH, MY GOD!
- NO, NO, NO!
[CHEERING]
NO, YOU MOTHERFUCKER!
- [DAVIS] FUCK!
- YEAH, I BET HE LIKED THAT ONE.
[CHEERING]
YEAH!
[JASON SCREAMS]
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
[PANTING]
IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT,
BRO, JUST STAY...
STAY WITH ME.
CALL AN AMBULANCE!
SOMEBODY CALL
THE FUCKING AMBULANCE!
[BRIAN WHEEZING]
[CRYING]
IS HE OKAY?
HE'S DEAD,
HE'S FUCKING DEAD!
[JASON]
NOT LIKE THIS.
BRIAN, SIT UP,
COPS ARE COMING, MAN.
DON'T YOU FUCKING DIE.
DON'T YOU FUCKING
LEAVE ME, MAN!
NOT LIKE THIS.
[PANTING]
[JADE SOBBING]
[JASON BREATHING HEAVILY]
[JADE]
NO!
[MICHELLE SOBBING QUIETLY,
SNIFFLING]
[MICHELLE]
WHAT DID YOU DO?
WHAT DID YOU JUST DO?
OH, MY GOD!
OH.
LORD, HELP ME.
HELP ME.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD,
WHAT IF HE'S DEAD?
[SCREAMING]
MICHELLE!
[MICHELLE]
WHY?
WHAT IF YOU KILLED HIM?
WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO?
[SOBBING]
[KING SCREAMING]
[JADE SOBBING]
[JADE]
NO!
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[KING] JUST... FUCKING
WAIT, DON'T LOOK AT HIM.
DON'T FUCKING
LOOK AT HIM.
[MICHELLE SOBBING SOFTLY]
Y'ALL DON'T HAVE TO
GO DOWN WITH ME, OKAY?
I'LL, UH...
I'LL TELL THEM THAT
Y'ALL WEREN'T IN THE CAR.
BUT WE WERE
IN THE CAR!
MICHELLE, I DON'T THINK
YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW SERIOUS THIS IS!
FUCK!
[CRYING]
NO...
NOT ME.
OH, GOD, NO, PLEASE.
[GROANS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
MOM...
MOM, YOU AND DAD
NEED TO COME UP HERE.
WESTERN PLAZA.
IT'S BRIAN,
SOMETHING HAPPENED.
IT'S BAD, MA.
I DON'T KNOW.
PLEASE, JUST...
JUST COME.
[PANTING]
[MICHELLE]
I REMEMBER...
IT BEING SO COLD.
UNUSUALLY COLD.
AND THERE WAS GLASS
AND METAL EVERYWHERE.
IT WAS CHAOS.
IT... IT WAS WORSE
THAN ANY NIGHTMARE.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
CODY'S THOUGHTS
THAT NIGHT
LAY IN INTIMIDATION,
IN FEAR.
BUT NOT HATRED.
YEAH, BUT WHAT HE DID
IS STILL WRONG.
AND YOU CANNOT
DEFEND WHAT HE DID.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER,
TAPPING ON DOOR]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[OFFICER]
CAN I HAVE THE KEYS, PLEASE?
CHUCK.
[CHUCK]
WHAT? WHAT DO YOU GOT?
[PROSECUTOR] WE BELIEVE THAT THE
EVIDENCE WILL CONVINCE YOU,
BEYOND A REASONABLE DOUBT,
THAT THIS WAS NOT AN ACCIDENT,
THAT THIS IS WAS
NOT JUSTIFIED, AND...
AND THAT THE DEFENDANT
INTENTIONALLY...
AND KNOWINGLY
MURDERED BRIAN DENEKE.
HE HAD NEVER ATTEMPTED
TO APPLY HIS BRAKES
OR TURN HIS STEERING WHEEL
AS HIS CADILLAC HAD
APPROACHED BRIAN.
HE HAD FLED THE SCENE
OF A CRIME
AND HE LIED
TO THE POLICE.
WHEN THE MEDICAL EXAMINER
HAD DESCRIBED
BRIAN'S INJURIES,
HE CONCLUDED THAT BRIAN
HAD REMAINED CONSCIOUS
AS HIS BODY WAS DRAGGED UNDER
THE... UNDERNEATH THE WHEELS
OF THAT CADILLAC.
THE IMPACT...
IMPACT SO SEVERE,
THAT HIS COLLARBONE HAD BEEN
TORN FREE FROM HIS SHOULDER.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
OUR YOUNG PEOPLE...
ON BOTH SIDES
OF THE AISLE
IN THIS COMMUNITY
NEED TO BE TOLD
BY THE 12 OF YOU
THAT WHAT YOU DO
CARRIES WITH IT
CONSEQUENCE.
NO MATTER WHO YOU ARE.
NO MATTER
WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE.
AND NO MATTER
HOW YOU DRESS.
I DON'T EXPECT
YOU TO ENJOY SENDING
THIS YOUNG MAN TO PRISON.
I DON'T.
I EXPECT YOU TO DO IT
WITH A TEAR IN YOUR EYE
AND YOUR HEART
IN YOUR THROAT.
PRESIDENT JOHN KENNEDY
SAID,
"WE DO THINGS,
NOT BECAUSE
THEY ARE EASY,
BUT BECAUSE THEY ARE HARD."
TODAY I ASK YOU
TO DO THE HARD THING.
I ASK YOU TO SEND A MESSAGE
TO THIS COMMUNITY
THAT ALL YOUNG PEOPLE,
ALL OF THEM,
WILL SUFFER THE CONSEQUENCES
OF THEIR ACTIONS,
AND THAT YOU ARE HOLDING
CODY CATES
UNCONDITIONALLY RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE DEATH OF BRIAN DENEKE.
"DESTROY EVERYTHING."
IS THIS THE MESSAGE WE WANT
TO SEND OUR CHILDREN
FOR GENERATIONS TO COME?
"DESTROY... EVERYTHING."
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THIS IS NOT A CASE
ABOUT DIVERSITY
OR TOLERANCE,
THIS IS NOT ABOUT
JUDGING PEOPLE FOR
THE WAY THEY DRESS.
THIS CASE
IS ABOUT A GANG
OF YOUNG MEN
WHO CHOSE A LIFESTYLE
DESIGNED TO INTIMIDATE
THOSE AROUND THEM,
TO CHALLENGE AUTHORITY
AND TO PROVOKE A REACTION
FROM SOCIETY
ITSELF.
WHEN THOSE PUNKS BROUGHT
BATS AND CHAINS
OUT THERE WITH THEM
TO WESTERN STREET
THAT NIGHT,
A CONSPIRACY WAS PUT
INTO PLAY
TO KILL AND MAIM THOSE
HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS.
CODY HAD NO TIME
TO THINK
OR PONDER,
HE HAD TO TAKE
IMMEDIATE ACTION
AND HE TOOK IT.
AND IF HE HAD TO LIVE IT
ALL OVER...
HE WOULD DO IT AGAIN.
YOU SEE,
WHAT CODY CATES FACED
OUT THERE THAT NIGHT
WAS A BAD COMBINATION:
A MEAN DRUNK WITH A WEAPON.
AND SOMEWHERE,
IN THE INFINITE PROCESSES
THAT SHAPE A BOY
INTO A MAN...
SOMETHING HAPPENED
TO BRIAN DENEKE.
THE MANNER OF HIS DEATH
WAS, UNFORTUNATELY,
THE END RESULT OF A LONG LIST
OF POOR CHOICES OVER
THE LAST SIX YEARS OF HIS LIFE.
YOU COULD EVEN ARGUE
THAT HE WAS DESTINED
TO DIE THE WAY HE DID.
HE WAS A VIOLENT INDIVIDUAL.
AND IT TOOK VIOLENCE
ON CODY CATES' PART...
TO PUT AN END
TO FURTHER VIOLENCE
AND TO SAVE
AN INNOCENT LIFE.
LET THIS BOY GO HOME.
RESTORE HIM
TO HIS FAMILY.
'CAUSE HE DID
THE RIGHT THING.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[REPORTERS CLAMORING]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[MARILYN MANSON ON TV]
THE ONE STORY THAT, UH...
THAT REALLY STRUCK ME
AND GOT ME THINKING ABOUT
THIS WAS, A FEW YEARS AGO,
THERE WAS THIS
TEENAGE PUNK ROCKER KID
WHO WAS RUN DOWN
BY A WHITE JOCK
IN DAD'S CADILLAC.
AND, UH...
THIS BOY DIED
BECAUSE HE LOOKED DIFFERENT.
SO THIS THING HAPPENS,
THIS GUY KILLS THIS KID,
AND IS CLEARLY GUILTY,
YOU KNOW,
HIS GUILT IS ADMITTED,
AND GUESS WHERE THIS
ALL-AMERICAN ATHLETE IS,
HE'S IN COLLEGE.
YOU KNOW, THE JURY FELT
THE PUNK ROCKER DESERVED TO DIE
BECAUSE HE LOOKED
THE WAY HE DID.
AND NOT ONLY WAS HE KILLED,
BUT THEN, IN THE TRIAL,
HE WAS KILLED AGAIN
BECAUSE THEY...
YOU KNOW,
CRITICIZED HIS LIFESTYLE
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T, YOU KNOW,
WEAR A TOMMY HILFIGER SHIRT
AND KHAKI PANTS, YOU KNOW?
AND THEN THE KILLER WAS EVEN
APPLAUDED AT GRADUATION
BECAUSE HE WAS
A FOOTBALL STAR.
THE AMERICAN DREAM,
STRONG, NORMAL.
HE NEVER A SPENT
A DAY IN PRISON.
SO WHO DO WE BLAME?
YOU KNOW?
EVERYBODY WANTS TO SAY,
YOU KNOW,
"TOO MUCH VIOLENCE,
TOO MUCH VIOLENCE TODAY,"
YOU KNOW?
[STAMMERS]
DID EVERYONE FORGET
ABOUT THE CIVIL WAR,
OR THE BIBLE,
OR SHAKESPEARE, YOU KNOW?
VIOLENCE
ISN'T BRAND-NEW.
THAT'S WHY I ASKED THE QUESTION,
YOU KNOW?
I PUT THIS UP
ON MY WEBSITE.
I SAID, "IS ADULT ENTERTAINMENT
KILLING OUR CHILDREN,
OR IS KILLING OUR CHILDREN
ENTERTAINING ADULTS?"
I THINK THAT'S KIND
OF THE QUESTION
WE GOT TO ASK
OURSELVES TODAY.
AND, YES, ASK YOURSELF
THAT EVERY TIME
YOU WATCH THE HUNGRY CAMERAS
AT THE CRIME SCENE,
OR AT THE FUNERAL,
OR AT THE PLANE CRASH.
YOU KNOW, I'M IN A SQUARE RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT ME,
I'M LOOKING AT MYSELF
IN A MONITOR, YOU KNOW?
WE SIT IN FRONT
OF THE TV
AND WE ARE THE TV.
WE'RE A COPY
STARING AT A COPY...
AT A COPY
AND A COPY.
EVENTUALLY IT'S A XEROX
THAT'S SO DEGENERATED,
WE DON'T KNOW
WHICH CAME FIRST.
AND THAT'S WHERE WE ARE.
AND THAT'S WHAT
I'D LIKE TO LEAVE YOU WITH.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BRIAN]
DON'T TELL ME WHAT TO DO,
I'M A FUCKING ANARCHIST!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
SUBTITLES BY EXPLOSIVESKULL
♪ WHAT'S YOUR REASON ♪
♪ FOR EXISTENCE? ♪
♪ DO YOU BELIEVE
IN ANYTHING? ♪
♪ OR DOES YOUR LIFESTYLE
CONTRADICT ♪
♪ THE WORDS YOU WRITE
FOR THE SONGS YOU SING? ♪
♪ SING ♪
♪ SING, SING ♪
♪ GET YOUR FREAK ON ♪
♪ ARE YOU HAPPY IN YOUR WORK AS YOUR
PROTEST ABOUT THE UNEMPLOYED? ♪
♪ YOU DON'T WANNA WORK, BUT YOU NEED THE
MONEY THE REALITY YOU CAN'T AVOID ♪
♪ DO YOU WANNA WORK,
DO YOU WANNA WORK ♪
♪ DO YOU REALLY WANNA WORK
FOR THE MONEY? ♪
♪ DO YOU WANNA WORK,
DO YOU WANNA WORK ♪
♪ DO YOU REALLY WANNA WORK
FOR THE SYSTEM? ♪
♪ ARE YOU HAPPY AS YOU VOTE
TO KEEP THE PARASITES ALIVE? ♪
♪ YOU DON'T WANT TO VOTE,
BUT YOU THINK YOU SHOULD ♪
♪ THEY SAID IT WAS RIGHT
AND YOU NEVER ASKED WHY ♪
♪ DO YOU WANNA VOTE, DO YOU WANNA VOTE, DO
YOU REALLY WANNA VOTE FOR YOUR CONSCIENCE? ♪
♪ DO YOU WANNA VOTE,
DO YOU WANNA VOTE ♪
♪ DO YOU REALLY WANNA VOTE
FOR THE SYSTEM? ♪
♪ HATE! ♪
[REPORTER 1] THE KILLING
OCCURRED DURING A FIGHT
BETWEEN THE PUNKS AND
A GROUP CALLED "THE PREPS,"
WHICH INCLUDED THE CHILDREN
OF SOME OF AMARILLO'S
WEALTHIEST CITIZENS.
[REPORTER 2]
BUT INSTEAD OF GOING TO PRISON,
HE WAS PUT ON PROBATION
AND ALLOWED TO GO FREE.
[REPEATING RAPIDLY]
FREE.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ MURDER! ♪
♪ THOUGHT WE SPLINTERED
IT AWAY ♪
♪ MEANS YOU GOT TO
KILL TODAY ♪
♪ MEANS THE LAW
WILL TAKE CONTROL ♪
♪ JOCKS ARE COMING,
WE GOT TO GO ♪
♪ MURDERED ♪
♪ WHAT A FUCKING SHAME ♪
♪ THE SYSTEM IS TO BLAME ♪
♪ MURDERED ♪
♪ THIS IS FUCKING LAME ♪
♪ BLAMED WHILE
THE RICH WILL ROLL ♪
♪ JOCKS ARE COMING,
WE GOT TO GO ♪
♪ NOT WITHOUT
THE BIGGEST LOSS ♪
♪ PLUS, WE'RE TAKING
ANY CAUSE ♪
♪ MURDERED ♪
♪ WHAT A FUCKING SHAME ♪
♪ THE SYSTEM IS TO BLAME ♪
♪ MURDERED ♪
♪ THIS IS FUCKING LAME... AH ♪
♪ THE SYSTEM IS TO BLAME ♪
♪ MURDERED ♪
♪ THIS IS FUCKING LAME ♪
♪ WHAT A FUCKING SHAME ♪
♪ MURDERED ♪
♪ THIS IS FUCKING LAME ♪
♪ BLAMED WHILE
THE RICH WILL ROLL ♪
♪ JOCKS ARE COMING,
WE GOT TO GO ♪
♪ NOT WITHOUT
THE BIGGEST LOSS ♪
♪ PLUS,
WE'RE TAKING ANY CAUSE ♪
♪ MURDERED ♪
♪ WHAT A FUCKING SHAME ♪
♪ THE SYSTEM IS TO BLAME ♪
♪ MURDERED ♪
♪ THIS IS FUCKING LAME... ♪
♪ AH ♪
♪ FUCKING FOLLOW US ♪
♪ FUCK YOU! ♪